My mom is so controlling!
Are you taking a video?
Make sure you're doing it right.
I don't want to go home yet!
She's so hopeless.
Let's go.
Isn't she a celebrity?
Savana! Maybe you want to come with us.
Why are you grabbing me?
Let us have fun with you.
Let go of me!
- Liam!
- Let go of her!
Why are you getting so drunk?
When we were still together
back in the old world,
you didn't even take a sip of alcohol.
Please, forget whatever you're feeling
right now.
I will also forget that we talked about this.
I love you so much.
- Guys, selfie!
- Wacky!
Welcome to our resort.
OMG, there is lots of food.
We're going to eat a lot!
We're going to swim.
Are we on vacation?
Why, Liam?
Are we going straight to work?
Okay, fine.
Sorry, Savana.
What really happened?
Why did you get drunk the other night?
Many people will do everything
to get to where I am right now.
But I feel like I'm a robot.
Via.
What are you doing here?
You didn't say you were coming.
I could have...
I could have let the receptionist assist you.
Via, what are you doing here?
Surprise!
I just thought I'd surprise you.
I reserved a room for myself, actually.
I hope that's okay, Savana.
Of course.
You're welcome here anytime.
You'll have fun here.
Yeah.
Actually, I'm only looking
for a change of scenery
so I can write articles for the magazine.
So, don't worry.
I won't bother your work.
You will never be a bother to us, Via.
Honestly, we finished quite a lot last night.
Really?
That's good.
Well, let me give you a tour.
Game.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ma'am. Enjoy your stay.
Yes.
Love...
Are you sure you want to
share this room with me?
I mean, I don't want to bother you.
I know you're writing.
We don't work 24 hours.
And we have time to unwind.
Are you sure?
Don't say I didn't ask.
- Are you doing okay?
- Yes.
This place is beautiful, Savana.
I admire you.
Imagine, at your age,
you were able to invest in your own resort.
You're just like...
Like that colleague of yours
who owns lots of properties.
Maxine, right?
That's her, right?
But there's an issue about her...
What is the issue about?
I'm not sure if it's true.
Honestly, I'm not into gossip.
What issue?
That she has a sugar daddy.
Via...
What?
I'm sure Savana doesn't have a sugar daddy.
You're the last person I'd think
who would use other people for money.
Come on, you're loaded.
Yes.
See?
I used my own money for everything I have.
Well, that's why I don't claim ownership
of all the hotels and resorts of my father.
Because they're not mine.
I'm just a fashion editor.
Via...
You are the best fashion editor
in the most prominent fashion magazine
in the country.
If you say it like that, come on.
I'm happy that you're here.
You can help Liam become
more inspired in creating our story.
Really?
I really hope my boyfriend
takes inspiration from me.
I don't know anything about film making.
But your love story...
You can come up with a good story from that.
On the contrary,
I think heartbroken people
write better stories.
It's more emotional. Right?
I'll leave you for now.
You can join me later, okay?
What do you want to do, love?
Actually, I'm already hungry.
Wait, Savana!
Yes?
We'll go with you.
- Cheers!
They'll get drunk again.
Is there something you want to say, Borj?
Huh?
Nothing, Boss Bro.
How about you?
You want to tell me something, don't you?
You and Ma'am Via have been together
for a long time now.
I knew it. He wants to say something.
I thought you'd break up
when she left to study abroad.
But when she came back...
Even after she came back,
you remained solid. Right?
Well, you've been through a lot.
How you started...
Imagine?
That's unbelievable.
She said you saved her life that day.
And then?
What do you mean and then?
I just told you about the rare opportunity.
Don't you remember it anymore?
You're strange.
All I want to say is that...
I understand Miss Via
if she doesn't want to lose you.
It's so hard to find...
that kind of love.
If I were you, Boss Bro...
I would treasure it.
Just get more drinks for us.
That's what I've been waiting for, Boss Bro!
I'll be right back.
- More!
- Body roll!
Do better!
Boss Bro!
Why are you getting him drunk?
- Look at him!
- Come on, Borj.
Really?
You don't have to pretend, Borj.
I know you love celebrities.
- It's your chance!
- Right!
Go, Borj! Enjoy!
Why don't you dance, too?
- Guys, guys, guys.
- Come on, Borj!
Guys!
- Let's get Tristan inside...
- Borj!
Borj, let's get Tristan inside. Come on.
Come on! I'm not done yet!
Deedee, please delete the video.
Why would I do that? I will sell this.
Kidding!
Right. That's right.
Tristan has money to burn.
Hey, hey! Hold on!
This is my phone.
How much would I get?
It was just a joke.
Miss Savana might get mad.
- Show them.
- Anytime now.
But Sir Liam, we should really kill the hero.
Because there's no redemption.
Leroy, isn't it enough redemption
to give Tristan's character a second chance?
- Sir...
- What?
He betrayed the woman he loved.
He almost destroyed
the leading lady's community.
Do you think the audience
can still accept him?
Yes!
They will accept him as long as he repents.
You know what, I agree with Leroy.
I agree! That's right.
The hero should be canceled.
He's a traitor.
Yeah!
Unfaithful and...
Even I could kill that man...
Actually, he and his mistress.
Looks like there is an issue.
You're right.
I think I've seen this somewhere.
I know!
A toast.
Here you go.
Let Liam rest. He's drunk, too.
Let's all go to bed.
You don't listen to me.
Guys!
This story should have a magical typewriter.
The hero will go back to the past.
He will use the magical typewriter
to do that.
That's it!
Hey.
Savana!
I said there's magic in the story!
What?
We need a magical typewriter!
They got separated
because of that darn typewriter!
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Savana, sorry. That's enough.
Sorry. This is embarrassing. Sorry.
No, I understand the feeling. We're even.
What do you think, Savana?
- What do you think?
- I'm sorry, Liam,
but we're not doing a fantasy movie.
In this world we live in,
we don't escape through magic.
We can only regret the things we did wrong!
Boss Bro, hey!
Boss Bro!
You need to shut up.
What's gotten into them?
Come on!
Let's bring him to the room.
No, I'm fine. Don't touch me.
- Love, let's go.
- I'm fine.
Let's go!
- I can manage.
- Let's go to the room.
Please, clean up everything.
Love...
Love.
Joyce...
Who are you?
Savana...
Savana, act.
Savana, you're overacting!
Savana...
Savana, cry!
Savana... Savana, don't eat that!
Savana, you look so fat!
What happened?
It's so hard not to have...
Guys!
Savana's video
where she's caught dancing in a bar
while she's drunk
is now viral on social media.
[Girl with Periwinkle Hair]
But wait, there's more!
The second part of the video
is hot off the press.
Savana wasn't just drunk.
She was badmouthing her mother!
Gosh, her relationship with her mother
is so toxic.
Savana...
Savana, cry.
Savana, Savana.
Savana, Savana...
Whoever spread your video is really annoying.
But I have to recover first from my hangover.
I don't have the energy yet to comfort you.
What did I do last night?
I can't remember anything.
Does Tristan remember what he did last night?
Luckily, Savana had your videos erased.
Otherwise, you will also go viral.
Wait.
Maybe we can tackle the issue
of cyberbullying in our story.
Miss Savana, I've seen your situation
in a K-drama before.
I won't be surprised
if you have a revenge plot.
I wonder what I'll watch
to relieve my stress.
Wait, what damage control can I do?
Savana might break down during our filming.
I will have to take care of a celebrity.
I hate this awkward silence.
I don't know what's on everybody's mind.
Especially you, Liam.
Who uploaded this?
I will surely get it from my mom.
Joyce, if only I could take
the burden off of your shoulder.
Savana.
Hans.
I came back
as soon I saw the video sent by my friend.
How are you feeling?
I didn't mean it.
I didn't mean everything
I said in the video, Hans.
I was drunk.
I don't want them to think badly of my mom.
Who is he? Do you know him?
Beats me.
I mean, I don't know him.
Maybe he's her non-showbiz boyfriend.
Have you talked to your mom already?
I'm going to find out now.
Hon.
Hi, Hon.
Sorry, we finished late
with our creative meeting.
I even took the train to get here faster.
Why are we here?
Our budget might not afford this place.
Honestly, I didn't want to eat.
But...
Come on. Let's put it here.
I'm glad you came.
There you go.
I was planning to text you
to say this was my mom's treat.
But you might not show up.
Come on. I can deal with your mom.
There.
Mommy, how are you?
So you're back from Thailand.
I made sure to come back
to be in my grandson's moving-up ceremony.
I just shipped
all the beauty products I bought.
So, Liam.
Do you still have the same job?
Yes. I still work at the TV network.
So, did you get promoted?
I'm still a writer.
There are lots of senior writers
who are ahead of me.
I'm glad you're still in showbiz...
Unlike Joyce,
who never went back to acting
after giving birth.
Don't worry, Mommy.
I'm taking care of my wife and my son.
Really?
I think it's the other way around.
Joyce makes more money
from selling insurance.
Mommy, please.
Why?
Are you going to defend your husband?
He's the reason my dreams for you got ruined.
Everything that has happened to us
was our choice.
Look at where you are now.
I don't know how to respond
to what people say about you.
That! Your fall from stardom!
Joyce, you know everything I've done for you,
for your career!
But what happened?
You ruined it!
You both ruined it!
Ma'am!
Excuse me.
Madam, aren't you a former sexy star?
Madam! I knew it! It's you!
Madam, my mother is a big fan of yours!
- And my father too...
- You know me?
Yes, Madam!
My father has a calendar
with your picture in it.
My neighbors get rowdy
whenever you appear on TV, Madam!
- My gosh!
- You're so beautiful!
Oh, thank you.
Madam, can I have a picture with you?
Sure, sure!
Sure.
- There.
- You're still so fresh, Madam.
You smell so good!
Can I have a fan sign, too, Madam?
I always bring this with me.
I know I will see you someday, Madam.
- Okay, sure.
- This is my mom and my dad.
- Fidel and Andeng.
- Okay.
- Okay, please smile, Madam.
One, two...
- Thank you, Madam.
- Thank you, thank you.
Sorry for getting so excited.
It's okay.
- Thank you, thank you.
- I'm at the other table...
Mommy.
Mommy, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I know...
I know you got hurt by everything I said.
I didn't mean it.
I don't care about what you said.
What I'm concerned about is that
you were caught on video, drinking!
You know you can't be seen drinking
because of your endorsements!
Really, Mommy?
Is that all you care about? Endorsements?
Yes!
- Money?
- Of course!
Don't you think
we should talk about the real issue?
Can't you see or feel
that I need even just a little space, Mom?
Just a little space!
Wow.
And you want to have control
over your life and career?
To be ordinary?
To drink every night? Get wasted every night?
Is that the life you want?
How about your image?
Do you want to be ordinary?
Go ahead!
If I had let you decide for yourself,
you would have probably
lost your career already.
You...
would have gotten pregnant.
There goes your career, just like that.
You're on your own now.
Maxine, you guys were
the only ones with me that night.
I think I saw you taking a video of me.
Who leaked the video?
Hey, Savana!
Don't you know that's slander?
That's why I'm asking you.
I don't know who did it. I already told you.
I don't know who's the girl with...
whatsoever hair
who uploaded your video, okay?
And why don't you look for her?
I want to know where the video came from!
I have no idea!
You were so drunk that night, Savana.
You didn't notice
that a lot of people were taking
a video of you.
So, please.
Don't drag me into your problem.
Savana.
She's a coward
for hiding in an alter identity.
Don't worry.
Hans, why are you here?
Did you cut short your trip to Mindanao
just to be here?
I know you have important things
that you need to attend to.
Savana...
The victims of land grabbing need you,
but you're here.
Savana, I've completed the initial work
in Mindanao.
And I was there as a human rights lawyer
to help the oppressed and powerless.
Like how you are in trouble
because of that online predator.
Don't worry.
I'm here to protect you.
But in every case you handle,
you know who's the victim.
But my problem is...
I know someone from the NBI.
I talked to him already.
He will help us find
that online streaming channel.
Thank you, Hans.
Thank you for being here.
I'm always here for you, Savana.
I promise we'll find a way to resolve this.
Everyone, I would like
to introduce Attorney Hans Arevalo.
Good afternoon. Nice to meet you.
He's a lawyer.
Perfect!
Hey.
Is he your boyfriend, Savana?
Well, I'm not ashamed to say
that I'm her suitor.
Hello, good afternoon.
- I'm Hans.
- Via.
Nice to meet you, Via.
Hans.
Liam.
So, Liam.
Are you the head of the creative team
that develops Savana's movie?
Yeah, creative manager.
Oh, that's nice.
I'm glad you're with Savana right now.
At least you know what she's going through.
Since you're in the same industry.
I'll do my best to find out
who uploaded the video.
That's what I promised Savana, too.
Hi, Hans.
Please help Savana.
You know a lot of people
in the Cybercrime Division.
Of course, Auntie. You can count on me.
Thank you for being so reliable.
And I can't wait for you
to become my son-in-law.
Anyway, we have to go.
I still have to clean up a lot of mess.
Okay, that's our last baggage.
Please bring it to the car.
Auntie, I'll convoy your car.
Okay.
Sir, are you going to join us
in the service vehicle?
It's up to you, Love.
It's fine by me.
Whatever you want.
It's okay with me to drive.
No, I'll go with Via.
We'll go ahead, then.
- We'll go ahead.
- Be safe.
Bye.
That's mine. Thank you.
Boss Bro.
I'll ride with them.
Looks like you and Ma'am Via
still have a lot to talk about.
- Bye, Ma'am Via.
- Be safe.
Let's go together, Borj.
- Why?
- Let's go.
- I can go by myself.
Let me have that.
Love.
About last night...
I'm sorry.
I got so drunk.
Did I say something inappropriate?
Love.
Joyce...
Joyce.
Never mind.
As you said, you were drunk.
Let's go home.
Are you keeping an eye
on Tristan and Savana's film?
The campaign period will begin
in a couple of months.
We need to make sure
that my godson's popularity will rise.
Don't worry, Uncle Ramon.
It's a tried and tested formula.
Your movies become blockbuster hits
before the campaign period.
I'm sure it will also work for Tristan.
The movie will help him win the elections.
But looks like we have a problem with Savana.
Cry.
Savana, you should shed tears
only through your left eye.
Savana... Savana, don't eat that!
Savana, you look so fat.
Are you going to sacrifice your queen, Uncle?
Check.
Checkmate.
Now you know.
There's something you need to sacrifice
to win.
I don't care who suffers, Liam.
I won't let you become the hero
in dad's eyes again.
Uncle.
One more game?
You got me there, Uncle.
What kind of juice is this?
Is this fresh?
Of course!
It's so fresh, just like you.
I like it even if there's no ice in it.
But it needs more sugar.
There's no ice
because we don't want you
to have a sore throat.
There's still a concert coming up.
But put more sugar next time, okay?
Noted, Madam!
I will make it sweeter for you next time.
True!
- Thank you.
- Of course, Madam. Anytime.
Okay, thank you. Bye!
Good evening.
Madam, we're ready.
Are you ready?
We're ready, too. Let's begin. Let's go.
- Let's do this.
- Yes.
Mom, why do we have to do this?
Didn't I say that I would clean up your mess?
- Let's go.
- Yes.
- Let's do this.
- Come on.
Okay.
A manager and a mother...
Those are the roles I play
in my daughter's life.
It is not easy.
There's only one thing on my mind.
My daughter's welfare.
I admit
that I am sometimes strict with Savana.
But it's normal for every parent, right?
And it's normal
for people her age to party...
- To have fun, right?
- True.
Those malicious videos of Savana
that came out...
People don't know that those were edited.
- Edited?
- Yes.
- Oh my God, edited.
- Spliced.
My God.
People will do everything
to bring others down.
I know.
They only showed the part
where Savana was venting out.
They didn't show the whole context.
The whole video.
I see.
So after everything,
Savana told me that she understands
where I was coming from,
being her manager and her mother.
She assured me...
that our relationship wouldn't change...
That she wouldn't change a thing.
Savana, dear.
Sweetie, come here.
Come here, dear. Sit beside your mom.
Go and sit by her side.
To those who watched my video...
It's true.
It was edited.
That's not what really happened.
I apologize to everyone.
I'm sorry...
Especially to you, Mommy.
I'm sorry. I love you so much.
I know that, Sweetie.
I know that.
Love, is something bothering you?
You've been checking your phone
since earlier.
Vergil keeps sending me messages.
He's calling for an emergency meeting
tomorrow at Blacksmith.
He won't say what it's for.
I want a cake.
Can you buy it for me, Love?
Yeah, sure.
[Contacts: Joyce]
[No results for "Joyce"]
Joyce?
Joycelyn Trinidad.
Who is this?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Via, I'm sorry.
Can we go home?
I still need to inform the team
about our emergency meeting.
You can call them now.
It's okay.
I still need to pack my things.
So I really need to go home.
I'll finish this cake first.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Do you want to try it?
No.
Good luck with your meeting tomorrow.
Thank you.
Arnel, the action scenes in this movie
should be more challenging
than what we did before.
- Okay?
- Okay. Go, Arnel.
- Show them what you got.
- Okay, go.
Show them, Arnel.
- Show them!
- Go, Arnel!
Go, Arnel!
There you go!
Oh my! Arnel.
- Go check on him, Megan.
- Arnel. What have you done, Torong?
- Arnel...
- Arnel, are you still alive?
- My God.
- Oh, my!
What? Is he okay?
He's still alive.
What were you doing, Torong?
- Hey.
- Arnel.
- You overdid it.
Arnel.
- Get up.
- Can you get up?
Sir, what is this audition for?
A movie or a wrestling team?
Come on, Arnel.
You've become rusty.
You used to be my best stuntman.
The movie has great vision.
This is action.
Okay?
But you know, this is not lovely for me.
Sorry, Director.
- Let's try it again.
- Okay.
- One more time.
- Come on, let's do it again.
Torong, be careful.
I don't want to bring anyone to the hospital.
- Be careful, Torong.
- Come on, Torong.
Go!
Arnel.
Arnel!
What the? Arnel!
Gosh.
Arnel, you should rest first.
Let's see the others.
- Okay, rest, Arnel.
- Okay, let's see the others.
Next one.
Next.
Torong, be careful.
Torong, Torong. Torong, be careful.
Torong.
- He beat everyone up.
- This is nuts.
Three, five...
Three, five, seven.
- Ask them to come back, okay?
- Okay.
Hi, Director.
- Sir.
- Hello, Sir.
- Hi, Sir.
Hello, Sir.
What do you have here?
We have an audition.
We have chosen
one of the action scenes already.
- It's getting less and less.
- Action teams.
From 100, here it is now.
This looks okay.
That one.
- Number three...
- His built looks good.
He's good with dialogue.
- This one?
- Yes.
This one is good.
That one is okay, Sir.
- Ask this one for a callback, too.
- Okay, I will.
- Next!
- Boss Bro...
Savana, Auntie.
Hello.
What is the agenda for today's meeting?
I've yet to find out for myself.
Good morning, everyone.
It's nice to meet all of you.
I can't wait to win this election.
I want to introduce to all of you
my new protégé.
My other godson, Josh.
Okay, let's win this election.
With Josh, you are the boss.
What are these clothes
that you got from Dmitri?
Did you choose these?
My God!
I know drag queens
who have better taste than this.
Have you shown these to Miss Via?
We've already sent her pictures.
There it is.
She sent me a message already.
You explain this to our boss.
"I want you to research a woman
named Joycelyn Trinidad."
Joycelyn Trinidad.
What did Miss Via say?
Not work related.
Go back to your work.
Go!
Hello, Miss. What's the tea about this woman?
About your other godson.
Is he sure about his identity?
I'm going to give this round
to you and your daughter.
Are you really serious about this?
Of course, Uncle.
This is the chance my father gave me
to prove myself.
I don't think you understand.
I want Josh to win the elections
through this film.
Hey!
Are you okay?
Oh, Liam. Have you really gone insane?
You can go against everyone
except Congressman Ramon.
If not, you'll get what you deserve.
I've found Joycelyn Trinidad,
the woman you told me to look for.